Lucy G. Barber 147 147
Stage
- Series 1
  - Vietnam Veterans Against War- Survey and Congressional Record, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Congress Anti NPAC, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Jerry Wilson Blog Info, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Congress Pro on NPAC, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - White House Anti - Democrats Mayday, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Congress - Anti- on Mayday or More, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - White House April 24, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - April 24 1971- DC Government (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - White House - 1971 April 26-30 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - DC Reports April 29-30, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - 1971 April 1- 23 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - 1971 Training Complete Demonstrator, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - 1971 April 25- 30 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Women and Mayday, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Nonviolent Action Research Project, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Congressional Record, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Mayday: The Case for Civil Disobedience, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - History/Misc. Articles, 1969-1994 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Anti-War Articles, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Anti-War Misc., 1971 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - May 1st Rock Concert, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - DC Police May 2nd, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - DC Police May 3rd, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - DC May 4th Reports, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - May 5 DC Police, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - May 6-7 DC Police, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Arrests and Protests May 5-6, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Opinion Poll May Day, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Post March - Rennie Darr's, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Aftermath Reports DC, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Telegrams, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - 1971 May 6 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Mayday - Overviews/Comments, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Coverage April 25 - May 1, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - May 2 Coverage, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Protest Articles May 3 1971 Coverage (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - White House May 1- 6, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - White House Mayday Media, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - White House Cost of Protests, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Congressional Hearings - House Internal Security Committee, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - DC Human Relations Report, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Public Defender Service, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Mass Arrests DC Reports, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Park Service Reports, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU), 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - American Civil Liberties Union Mayday Work, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Order without Law Report, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Court Case American Civil Liberties Union, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - May 5th Demos, undated (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Mothers Day, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Vietnam May 9- District /Federal Policy, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Veterans Movement in the USA Comintern, 1934 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Executive Order 11605, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - San Francisco Mayday Plans, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Gays and MayDay, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Clearing Potomac Park, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - 1971 Other Demos - DC - May 8 Dec. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Subsequent Vietnam Veterans Against War, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against War Post DC Resignations, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against War vs. New York Peace Action Coalition, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - 1971 Aftermath - Vietnam Veterans Against War Post (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Anti War Magazine, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against War FBI infiltration 1972, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against War Dewey Canyon III Memories, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against War Split UP, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Court Cases- Guardian, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Post Mortem, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - DC Prison Report on Mayday, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Afterwards, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - National Peace Action Coalition Aftermath - Rivalries, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - 1971 Notes to File, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Post 9/11/01 Restrictions, 2011 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against War Aftermath, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - May 7-30 - 1971 DC (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - White House - 1971 Post Demo May (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Citizenship Forum, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Citizenship vs Post Civil War - Kaczorowki Article, undated (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - David Zaret Citizenship Articles, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Habermas - The Public Sphere, 1989-1996 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Value of Demonstration, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - White House/Capitol Photos, undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Police General, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Labor, undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Liberal Progressive Reform, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Public Sphere/ Feminist, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Margaret Somers Citizenship, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Putnam's Bowling Alone, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Manbridge - Feminism and Democracy, undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Urban Planning and City, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Public Sphere- China, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Fairfield - Review on Public, undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Fairfield, 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - "Democracy isn't What you Think" and "Citizenship is Malleable", 1996 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Police Performance - Theory, undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Galston - Won't you be my Neighbor?, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Kelman - Public Choice, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Mitchell - Public Space, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Edelman Space and Order, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Book Stuff, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Interlibrary Loan Request, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - American Civil Liberties Union Records Grade, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) Records, undated (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Sources to Look At- Primary, 1987-1996 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Register of the Anna Holden Papers, undated (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - National Capital Parks - Suitland Records, undated (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - National Archives: Office of Civilian Defense (OCD), 1996 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Movie Sources - National Archives, undated (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Washington - People to Call?, undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Zip Parallel Part - Users Guide, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Washington - To Do, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - State Historical Society of Wisconsin, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Social Movement Theory, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Herbst - Numbered Voices, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Original Introduction, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Pre 1894 Calls to Go to Washington, undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Right of Petition, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Change in Economy - Smith to Service Decline of Manufacturing, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Lincoln's Legacy Review, 1993-2000 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Lincoln Memorial Photographs, undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - The Record- National Archives Newsletter, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Oral History Notes, undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Schlesinger - Check Out, undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Library Work, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Misc. Sources, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Moorland Spigarn Fax, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Mimeograph, undated (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Lyndon B. Johnson Library, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Charles Tilly Article, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Right to Assembly, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Crowd, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - New Protests, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - University of California Press Maps, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - 1941 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - 1941 Ideas, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Photo Bonus - 1932, 1998-2000 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - 1941 Figures (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - March Photos, undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Introduction, undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - DC Population, undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Demonstration Info, undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Right to Privacy, undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Family/Market Privacy Pros, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Public/Private Politics, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Realism/Idealism/Futurism, undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - McGerbert - Intro and Coxey, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Waters interview, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - DC History - Recap, 1914-1917 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Students for a Democratic Society - 1963 March on Washington (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Scott Sandage's Oral History, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Sandage Correspondence, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Civil Rights Movement, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Dudziak Article - Desegregation, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Lobbying, 1913 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - 1970 - Anti War Magazines (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Million Man March, 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Misc. Photos, undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Million Man March, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - 1980s Internet and Protest, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Promise Keepers, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - March on Life (1997/98), 1998 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Solidarity Day, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - AIDS Articles, undated (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - New Conclusion, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Supreme Court on 1882 Law, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - American Civil Liberties Union Guide, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Conclusion WWII Sting Fight, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Civil War, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Pro Choice, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Troublemakers Article, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Victory Day, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Gay Lesbian March Articles, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - AIDS Quilt, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Arrest Protest 4/6/00, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Million Man March 5/14/00, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - 1967-1973 White House and Million Men's March, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - ALB Protest - Legal, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Million Family March 10/16/00, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Misc. March 1970/80/90, 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Experienced Organizers, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Trucker's Protest, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Anti Choice, 1988-1992 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - ERA, 1978-1990 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - 1985 Peace Ribbon (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Foreign Demonstration, 1992-1993 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Million Man March, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Million Man March ( 1 of 2), 1996 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Million Man March ( 1 of 2), 1996 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - World Trade Organization Protests, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Campaign, undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Harbinger of Change, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Randolph Blog, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - September 23 1940 Meeting Controversy (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - View of Lobbying, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Gerstle Article, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Opening Press Release, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Executive Orders - History, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Gandhi, undated (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - "Call" March on Washington, undated (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Key Pressure Bulletin, undated (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Selection Service, 1940 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Defense and Race ---- 1940, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - DC NAACP, 1940 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Agitation on Defense 1/41-3/41, 1940 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Democracy and Blacks, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Citizenship "I Am American", 1941 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - We Over Article - Defense Work II Citizenship, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Support of March, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Finances of March, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Organizing Feb March 1941, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Organizing April 1941, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Organizing May, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - James Finley Wilson, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Lobbying and Civil Rights Groups, 1941 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Experience Lieutenants, undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - NNC Picketing, undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Opposition to March 1941, undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Radical Support - Workers Party - Socialist, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Davidson and The New Negro Alliance, undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - White Press, undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Report: Segregation in Washington, 1940 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Washington Police, undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Protests - Civil Rights 1941, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Roosevelt on Washington Architecture, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Finkle - Conservative Aims, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Gender and March, 1940 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Mid March 1941, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Meeting for Executive Order 8802, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Picketing - Pacifists, 1941 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Defense and Minority Groups, 1940 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Foreign Context, 1941 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Roosevelt Mary Mcleod Bethune Correspondence and Nots from Baltimore Afro- American, 1941-1994 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - 1941 Pacifist Activities, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Media, undated (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Politics of Issue, 1941 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - My Account of Meetings, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Walter White on Demonstrating, 1948 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - FDR and Race (Morrison), 1969 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Goodwin - FDR and Eleanor Roosevelt, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Rayford Logan's Oral History, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - History Theory Paper, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - American Bartleby, 1923 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - American Pre 1860 John Higham, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Fight Over Hearings Pittsburgh Courier - NAACP, 1941 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Complaint on Order/Cancellation, 1941 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Praise for Order, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Composition of Fair Employment Practices Committee, 1941 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Security in Washington, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Security in Washington, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Aftermath Police, 1941 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Planning Future July, 1941 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - March on Washington Movement 1/42-6/42, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Legacy of March on Washington Movement - Pro, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Randolph and Fair Employment Practices Committee March, 1946 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Late 1940s - Anti Military - Segregation, 1948-1953 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Race - Aftermath - 1940s, 1941-1942 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Interracial Pilgrimage, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - 1940s Marches, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Legacy of March on Washington - Negative, 1942-1943 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Plans for DC Rally, undated (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - DC Regulation Against Parades, undated (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - "What the Negro Wants", 1969 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - The President and the Suffragists, 1913 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Picketing, 1917 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - WS Sources - Notes, undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Women's Suffrage Outline, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Women's Suffrage, undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Comments - Women's Suffrage, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Barnett - Post March Activism, 1943 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Women Suffrage Movement - 1900-1920 By Lucy Barber, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Washington Park System, 1902-1903 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Young DC Police Department, 1908 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - American Journal of Sociology Walter B. Bodenhafer, 1920 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - 1913 Group Theory, 1913-1915 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Women's Suffrage - Context - Demonstrations, 1916 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Women's Suffrage Context - Demonstrations, undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Wilson on Picketing, undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Women's Suffrage Article, undated (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - 1913 Interracial ban on marriage (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Cinema/Gender Rabinovitz, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - 1913 National American Woman Suffrage Association - 1910 Meeting (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - New York Woman Suffrage, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Army and Woman Suffrage Parade, 1913 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Marco De Marinis Dramaturgy of the Spectator, undated (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Inauguration 1905 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - 1913 Chicago Coverage March 2-10th (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Inauguration 1909 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Newspaper Coverage - Suffrage, 1913 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - 1913 LA Times (Suffrage Coverage) (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Davis V. Massachusetts Supreme Court, undated (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - 1913 Law, undated (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Crowds, 1912 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Suffrage Parade, 1913 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Karen Blair - Hazel Mackaye, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Women's Suffrage - Memoirs/Local Histories, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Parades and Happy Demonstration inauguration, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Mr. Dooley Women's Suffrage, 1917 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - 1900 Central Washington Map, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Police - 1910s Labor, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Temperance Folks, undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Lucy Burns, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - 1913 New Lobbying, 1906-1913 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Women and Citizenship, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Women and Beauty, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Context: Salvation Army, undated (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Context: Politics, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - 1910s Revolution - Women and Morals, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Crisis - Women's Suffrage, 1913 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Women's Suffrage - Articles/Magazines, 1913 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - African American Women Struggle, 1912-1913 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Context - Race and Women, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - 1913 Barnett Incident (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Women Suffrage Dubois - Harriet Stanton Blatch, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Woman Suffrage Articles (Not useful to dissertation), 1990 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Secondary Article - Suffrage, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - National Women's Party, 1982-1992 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Suffrage 1917 ( 1 of 2), 1991 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Suffrage 1917 ( 1 of 2), 1991 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Suffrage 1918, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - March 1994 Notes (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - National Coordinating Committee 11/15/65 March, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - 1965 Anti Vietnam March (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - 1962 Washington Peace March (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - 1966 Demonstrations - National Coordinating Committee (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - 1968 Women's Protest, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - 1967 Anti Vietnam March (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Better Barriers, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - 1965/66 National Park Service Policy, 1965-1966 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - DC Policy, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Hearings to Ban Protests, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Poor People's Campaign - National Park Service, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Poor People's Campaign/Nationwide Welfare Rights Organization, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Poor People's Campaign/Bonus Army, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - DC Archives Office of Emergency Preparedness, undated (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - 1969 White House Demonstration Policy (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - 1969 Protests (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - New Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - 1969 Park Police Review (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Anti War Movement General, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - 1970 Demonstration (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - White House Response to Demonstrations, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - 1970 May 9 - Cambodia Debates, 1965-1970 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Congress Investigations Jan 71', 1971 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - 1971 Feb 10 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - 1971 Jan - Feb (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - MLK Holiday Protest 1/15/71, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - White House - 1969 Protest Moratorium (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - 1971 Vietnam Movies Library of Congress, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - SDS Papers, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Nixon Materials, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - April 10 - Women's March, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - National Park Service Metro Police Agreement, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - 1971 Government Defense Plan (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - White House - 1971 March (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - White House - 1971 January - February (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Demolition of Buildings on the Mall, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - DC Representative, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Capitol Bombing Case, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - 1971 March 1st Capitol Bombing (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Hippies - Context, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Right to Assemble, 1967-1973 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Anti War Movement Overview, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Vietnamese Calls to Protest, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Definition of Violence, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - 1971 Law Week Supreme Court Opinions, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Janette Rankin Brigade, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Police and Riots, undated (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - White House - 1970 Top Secret Funding Sources (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - 1971 Lerner Overview Articles (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Initial Calls for Disruption, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - 1970 Demonstration Hearings (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - 1971 Rennie Davis - Blog, 1964-1971 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - John Kerry, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Al Hubbard - Biography, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - 1971 Brad Little, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - 1971 May 8 Victory March, 1970-1971 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - March for Victory, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Congressional Record Communists/Spring, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Cartoons - Doonesebury, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Peace Coalition for Peace and Justice Background, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Vietnam Veterans and Against War Background, 1967-1970 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against War General Histories, undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - 1971 Supreme Court and Vets, undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against War, 1969-1971 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against War Operation Raw, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - National Peace Action Coalition - 1970 Creation (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - National Peace Action Coalition January - February, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - 1971 March - 1971 National Peace Action Coalition (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - DC Permit Request National Peace Action Coalition, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - National Peace Action Coalition Budget, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - National Peace Action Coalition General, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against War and International Movements, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Vietnam Veterans - Winters Soldiers Investigation 1/30- 2/1/71, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against War - John Kerry, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against War and Film and Sound, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against War vs. National Peace Action Coalition, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against War vs Peace Coalition for Peace and Justice, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - January - March Newspaper Coverage, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - 1971 Magazine and Newspaper Coverage April 1-14, undated (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against War April 19-23, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Magazine Comment April 16-30 1971 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - May Comment on April, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Spring Offensive or Spring Rituals Article, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - April 19-23 DC Planning, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - White House - 1971 April 1-23 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Authorities and Protest Feiffer Cartoon, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - George Wiley and Larry Rub Collection Cassette Tapes, undated (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Oversized Maps - Federal Writers' Project, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)